Okay family, well I think the topic
Bueno familia pues yo creo que el tema
of the day has
del día
definitely been yesterday's interview
ha sido sin duda la entrevista de ayer
with Jesulín. I don't know what you thought. I've been
de jesulín no sé qué os pareció he
watching some clips. Javi was
estado viendo algunos extractos Javi
leaving the channel.
salía de canal
Hey, but you guys also follow that
Oye pero ustedes también seguís ese
anime. Yesterday we dropped a
anime ayer dimos un ayer dimos un buen
bombshell yesterday. Hey, yesterday we dropped a
bombazo eh ayer dimos unos buenos
bombshell. Your Honor is lost. Javi.
bombazos la señoría va perdida Javi
Because what Your Honor has to do
Porque la señoría lo que tiene que hacer
is also continue, not with
también es seguir no en
Javier, with the little one, where there's also
Javier en el canijo que también hay
a lot of gossip.
mucho chisme
Red man. How are you? How are you? Are you
hombre rojo qué tal estáis qué tal estás
showing up here so far?
apareciendo por aquí hasta ahora
How are you? Rum, well, let's watch Jesulín's interview.
Cómo estás ron bueno a ver la entrevista
Jesulín's interview. I've been
la entrevista de jesulín he estado
watching some scattered clips. Okay, I
viendo algunos clips salteados vale me
consider myself a good father. I consider myself a good
considero buen padre Me considero buen
husband and a good friend. I consider myself a very
marido y buen amigo y me considero muy
good friend. I also consider myself a very good
buen amigo y también me considero muy
enemy of my enemies. A
enemigo de mis enemigos
good father, good father, good husband,
buen padre buena buen padre buen marido
good husband, and a very good enemy of my
buen marido y muy enemigo de mis
enemies. But here comes, I think, one of
enemigos pero aquí viene yo creo uno de
the, I mean, there were a couple of headlines, they
los o sea hubo un par de titulares no
were like, he takes them out powerfully, like they
que fueron como los saca potente como si
were, he takes them out powerfully, like I
fueran lo saca potente potente como yo
put the headlines, not from these days.
he puesto los titulares no de estos días
The host, no, the slap.  without hands to
la [__] no la el bofetón sin manos a
Belén Esteban that we know each other a little
Belén Esteban que nos conocemos un poco
I know that you are taking great care of the
Yo sé que tú estás cuidando mucho la
privacy of this floating child who
privacidad de este niño flotante que
is taking great care of the privacy of
está cuidando mucho la privacidad de
this child and he says no no his and
este niño y él dice no no la de él y la
everyone's exactly I have
de todos exactamente
pending accounts with this house
tengo cuentas pendientes con esta casa
precisely I have pending accounts
precisamente tengo cuentas pendientes
with this house
con esta casa
okay I
vale
think he is referring to the sentence not to the
creo que se refiere a la condena no a la
sentence that they recently gave
condena que le han puesto hace poco
to the television factory and to Kiko
a la fábrica de la tele y a Kiko
Hernández for
Hernández por
Jules okay then he also has another
Jules vale luego que tiene también otra
then he also has another other
luego que tiene también otra otras
lawsuits that are out there being appealed
demandas que están por ahí recurriéndose
that he has also won I think it is one
que él también ha ganado creo que es una
that is directly against Mediaset
que es a mediaset directamente
because they accused him of infidelity
porque lo acusaron de una infidelidades
with people from the corridors of Telecinco
con gente de los pasillos de telecinco
something like that a move like that well
algo así una movida así
delighted to see you like this I am face
pues encantada de verte así estoy cara
blowing a kiss Good night ro I am
lanzando un beso Buenas noches ro Me
glad to see you here a huge kiss
alegro de verte por aquí un beso enorme
gorgeous
guapísima
and what I do have very clear
y yo lo que sí tengo muy claro
very clear is that I am going to defend tooth and
muy claro es que voy a defender A capa y
nail the
espada la
privacy the total and
privacidad la privacidad total y
absolute privacy of my children of the four I am not
absoluta de mis hijos de los cuatro no
going to force any line that could
voy a forzar ninguna línea que pueda
harm my children in any
perjudicar a mis hijos en cualquier
way no and of course I am not going to
aspecto no y por supuesto no voy a
cross any  line that could
cruzar ninguna línea que pueda
harm my children an aspect ok
perjudicar a mis hijos un aspecto vale
with what he's telling you apart from the fact
con esto que te está diciendo aparte de
that he has the children equally with this he
que tiene a los hijos por igual con esto
's telling you that he's not going to give it a
te está diciendo que no le va a dar
roll and that he's not going to give it to Belén
rollo y que no le va a dar bola a Belén
Esteban okay this is what he's telling you
Esteban vale es lo que te está diciendo
here
aquí
and I'm very clear that I have to
y tengo muy claro que
respect the will I'm
tengo que respetar la voluntad
going to defend it they
lo voy a defender
are respecting it
lo estén respetando
well it's that if they do
bueno
n't respect it there will obviously be a problem with
es que no lo respete tendrá problema
things nowadays with the networks and
las cosas hoy en día con las redes y
so on what I say is curious that he
demás que digo que es curioso que nos
has leaked my photos nothing at all
haya filtrado mis fotos nada ni nada
in photos they can't be leaked If you don't let's
en fotos no se pueden filtrar Si tú no
see if you don't If
vamos a ver si tú no Si tú no subes
you don't upload any photos of If you don't upload any
ninguna foto de Si tú no subes ninguna
photos of your children anywhere there's no
foto de tus hijos ninguna parte no hay
way it can be leaked it can be leaked
manera de que se filtre se puede filtrar
if you have the account locked or if
si tú tienes la cuenta en candado o si
you put it on WhatsApp I
tú la pones en el WhatsApp yo es que le
even scold my parents when they put
rino incluso a mis padres cuando ponen
if they put photos of the children on WhatsApp
si ponen en WhatsApp fotos de los niños
the photo doesn't have to be put
la foto no las tiene porque poner en
anywhere I mean the photos are for you they
ningún lado o sea las fotos son para ti
're for us so why do you have to
son para nosotros para que la tienes que
put them on Facebook or WhatsApp
poner en Facebook ni en WhatsApp en
anywhere so that others can see the
ninguna parte para que vean los demás
children that they have Well no that's it
los niños que tienen Pues no ya está
We know  the children that we have,
Nosotros sabemos los niños que tenemos
you put in, since you put in a few
tú pones desde que tú pones una unas
lines and you are the first one who doesn't
líneas y tú eres el primero que no las
pass them, you have to respect
pasas las tiene que respetar a todo el
everyone and your family agrees on
mundo y tu familia está de acuerdo en
this,
esto
the family is very much in agreement
la familia está muy de acuerdo
Maria,
María
I have a very good thing with my wife, we
yo tengo una cosa muy buena con mi mujer
talk about everything, well it seems to me we
que todo lo hablamos pues me parece todo
talk about everything, the good, the bad, the
lo hablamos lo bueno lo malo las
decisions, it
decisiones
surprised me, funny that I'm
ya me extrañaba gracia de que estoy
talking out there,
hablando por ahí
Belén is going to explode, well no, in fact, she's already
Belén va a explotar bueno no de hecho ya
exploded a little, no, now we'll see, she
explotado un poco no ahora lo veremos
has it very well with Federico, look at it, let's
lo tiene muy bien en Federico míralo a
see,
ver
but not me, but what do I have to see
pero no a mí pero qué tengo que ver
Pilar, all the videos that they've
Pilar todos los vídeos que me han
sent me, look at it but let's see. They sent me
mandado míralo pero a ver Me han mandado
eight videos of Federico, Pilar, I have
ocho vídeos de Federico Pilar que tengo
to see all eight, what we
que ver los ocho
think, like what we can
lo que opinamos como lo que podemos
advise, my wife and I, we are dolls, let's go, we
aconsejar mi mujer y yo somos muñecas
both as one. How good, how
vamos vamos los dos a una Qué bien qué
good in all of them, I send her a
bien en todos los que le mando yo un
kiss
beso
and in all the circumstances that we
y en todas las circunstancias que nos
see each other. And the truth is that it has gone
veamos Y la verdad es que nos ha ido
quite well for us, I'm going to be 21 years old,
bastante bien voy para 21 años
21 years old, my goodness,
21 años madre mía
Jesús, Ubrique says, in my house it is
Jesús lindo ubrique dice en mi casa es
yours with his song is still in the
la tuya que con su canción sigue en
front line and only a
primera línea y eso solo lo hace un
genius can do that
genio
my song still after
mi canción todavía después de
twenty-something years I'm still
veintitantos años
there in the front line
sigo ahí en primera línea
that the song is still in the front line
que la canción sigue en primera línea
this one says
dice este
damn where do you put Jesulín where does it say
[__] dónde pones jesulín dónde pone
Esolín where do you put Jesulín
esolín dónde pones jesulín
but what do I have to see
pero que tengo que ver
Jesulín turn that is the first
jesulín convertir eso es primera
interview in a long time it's also
entrevista en mucho tiempo es además en
live I mean not on Hola like the ones
directo quiero decir no en Hola como las
we used to watch and a
que solíamos ver y una audiencia
relative audience of 11.2 is what they did last night
relativa 11,2 es lo que hicieron anoche
in that premiere of the last season
en ese estreno de la última temporada
the sticks minus the red lines that he
los palos menos las líneas rojas que él
had asked please that could not be
había pedido por favor que no se podían
mentioned which are the usual ones Belén
mencionar que son las de siempre Belén
Esteban and Andrea Janeiro I don't understand
Esteban y Andrea Janeiro yo no entiendo
this insistence of Jesulín of not wanting to
este empeño de jesulín de no querer
talk about Belén when she has been part of
hablar de Belén cuando ha sido parte de
his life and is the mother of his eldest daughter
su vida y es la madre de su hija mayor
But I imagine that he doesn't want to
Pero me imagino que no quiere
ring the bell
echarle al timbre
Why not Bertín said because
Por qué no Bertín dijo porque también a
Belén too and he didn't want to create bad vibes and
Belén y no le apetecía crear mal rollo y
that there would be controversy
que hubiera polémica
if possible but if it is that also That
si es posible pero si es que además Eso
is more seen than him I see you what I don't
está más visto que él te veo lo que no
understand is  about the daughter Let's see also
entiendo es lo de la hija A ver también
It's true that the daughter doesn't want to go out No
Es verdad que la hija no quiere salir No
but come on she does
pero vamos
n't want to go out another thing is that the
no quiere salir otra cosa es que el
father doesn't refer to her he referred to the
padre no se refiera a ella se refirió
four children I know I
los cuatro hijos
know that he was a soccer player
lo sé lo sé que era un futbolista
the other was also a soccer player
el otro también era futbolistas
of the let's see if he tries now Castilla I
de la a ver si intenta ahora el Castilla
don't know he has nine left eh
no sé le quedan nueve eh
but you don't know he even made a bullfight
pero no sabes hizo hasta una corrida
just for women
solo para mujeres
Well then specifically
Bueno pues el concretamente
defend and Leo verbatim privacy cloak and dagger we
defender y Leo textual A capa y espada
comment on it in our
la privacidad lo comentamos en nuestro
documentary
documental
say
diga
league
liga
who is
quién es
[Music]
[Música]
and I can't be ashamed either
y yo se puede tener tampoco vergüenza
my mother do you remember that lady
madre mía os acordáis de esa señora
really there are people who there are no
de verdad hay gente que no
people who education and
hay gente que la educación y la
shame no
vergüenza no
my mother do
madre mía
you remember a lady who came up here
os acordáis una señora que subió aquí
insulting the one who messed around lacked respect for
insultando la que lió faltó respecto a
the family you
la familia
can have let's go you can have
se puede tener vamos se puede tener
less shame I say there are people who
menos vergüenza digo hay gente que de
really have education
verdad la educación
and are starting to call like
y se está poniendo a llamar como de
really there are people who education and such have
verdad hay gente que la educación y tal
not been given that was in the scoundrel it
no se la han dado eso fue en el canijo
was not the scoundrel But do you remember a
no fue el canijo Pero os acordáis una
lady there lacking respect who is
señora ahí faltando al respeto que está
terrible evidently there are no people who
fatal evidentemente no hay gente que la
education of  It's true that they haven't given it to him at
educación de verdad no se lo han dado
all, of my children of the four, that's
absoluta de mis hijos de los cuatro es
what he said and at one point he also lets
lo que dijo y en un momento además deja
slip or makes a mention of the problems
caer o hace una mención a los problemas
he has with that house, he says I have
que él tiene con esa casa dice tengo
outstanding accounts with this house, he's
cuentas pendientes con esta casa se
referring to Mediaset or as Belén
refiere a mediaset o como dice Belén
Esteban says now, Belén Esteban said, of course,
Esteban ahora Belén Esteban dijo Claro
because it came out, of course, hours before
porque brotó por supuesto horas antes de
the interview, Belén was already
la entrevista Belén ya estaba
absolutely hysterical,
absolutamente histérica
she says this company, says Mediaset,
ella dice esta empresa dice mediaset
Mediaforo or whatever it's called now,
mediaforo o como sea que se llame ahora
no
no